{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"﻿auti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"autorči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"avionči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"balkonči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"balonči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bazenči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bezosje","osnova2":"ajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bezosje","osnova2":"ajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bezosje","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bicikli","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bjelokoš","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"Boži","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"boži","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bubnji","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"nuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"budu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"budu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvje","osnova2":"arna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvje","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvjeti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"čeki","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"često","osnova2":"a-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elavac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elavčev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elavost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"evapči","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ilim","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"irilica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"irilični-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ud","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"up","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"urlikati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"urliknuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"desetlje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dječači","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dječači","osnova2":"ev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dobro","osnova2":"udan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dobro","osnova2":"udno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dobro","osnova2":"udnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ičin-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"inov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"inski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"došaš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"džepi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"đavolči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"đavolči","osnova2":"ev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"gospi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"goš","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"gradiš","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"gusto","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"hladno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"idu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ivani","osnova2":"gradski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"izi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"izvješ","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"izvu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"janje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"jare","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"jari","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"june","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kafi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erinski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kozle","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kozli","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"križi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"aninov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"ankin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kruži","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"aničin-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kune","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kuni","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kuni","osnova2":"evina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kvadrati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lanči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lavi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lavi","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"listi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lonči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lovre","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mači","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"eha","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ehin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ehinski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"uhica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"masno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"medvjedi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"miši","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"nesre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"oku","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"op","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"op","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"palči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pam","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pile","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"plu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"poduze","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"polno","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"posti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"postoje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pove","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"predboži","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prihva","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prije","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"primje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pročiš","osnova2":"ivač-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prona","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prsti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pure","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"rači","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ražnji","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"rupči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"si","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sino","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sljede","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"snjegovi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"spava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"srnda","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"srne","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"staja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"stanči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"stolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"suho","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svije","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svije","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svinje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svje","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"štapi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tele","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"aš","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ašev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ašica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ašičin-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"trokuti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"trudno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uop","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"upu","osnova2":"enost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uve","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"valjči","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"arna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vrti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vuči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"zada","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"zeči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
